[{"answer": "When do I get to meet him", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Never", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What answer were yo", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I take a straight 15 percent. my friend's fee varies with risk. Perhaps you'd be more comfortable using someone else", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Other than me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "This is fucked. You don't know in tha", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You're goddam right you jumped the gun", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " I'm doing a transfer now", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I'll come straight there", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Yes", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Federal Express", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's fine", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You'd like to buy your wife some lingerie as a Christmas gift", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How 'bout Christian Dior", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Very good", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Pardon", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Eight.  Size eight", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How can I reach you", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Are you still in Crystal City", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I think you're taking it seriously enough for both of us", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I love my blender", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, but they took my blender", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. Detective that place", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Your stuff", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Witnesses said you were there, but I notice you didn't file a report", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A police report", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "there", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "the store, the accident was outside. It was a bus", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Someone said you spoke to Mr. my friend before he died. I thought you might know something", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "About the accident", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm no expert, but I'm assuming that the impact of a moving bus against his body cause", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What kind of trouble", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "He got hit by a bus", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I honestly don't know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend was involved in an extortion scheme. We believe he passed you sensitive materials, possibly with your knowledge, and we need t", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "We believe he did", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You're wrong", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "If he passed me materials, I'd have them. I don't", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "m", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Otherwise you may have to what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "m", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Otherwise you may have to what", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Into what", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm a labor lawyer. There are mob ties", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": ". Someone's mixing up a bunch of hal", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Maybe my friend. Maybe the unions. I don't know", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "my friend, I found out like this. This is the first I'm  o", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You had an affair with this woman, my friend, we went to a fucking for a year", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You told me you weren't seeing her at ", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "footage, for God's sake. I don't see how he could've slipped you something that the that place would be interested in", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "your point", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " Your shoe", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Gimme the shoe", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I don't know anything about my friend", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "said he was behind an extortion scheme", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " 30 minutes ago you said we had him. What in hell's goin' on out there", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " Help from whom?  Christ", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "your name, I don't know  the hell you did for me except hang up on my wife and slam me into a wall, but I'm getting pretty fuckin'  of this! Get it?", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I sit on top of the greatest intelligence gathering organization in human history. Why can't I bring in a man whose name ?", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "He's clever? He had help?  Oh", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Listen to me", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, listen to me. You gotta let me bring you in", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "No, ", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "it to the police. They won't let me get there. You go", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "The lingerie", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I was missing you", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Having an adventure. I can't tell you about it right now, but I'll tell you about it soon", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "No. We're never getting a divorce. We were having a fight. It happens sometimes", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I taped it off the 11 o'clock news", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "I was worried about my hundred and twenty 'K'", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Did you call anyone", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I mean did you call anyone", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "What'd I tell you", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I told you no calls", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "What do you think", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Welcome to that place's Workshop", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Oh, let's assume that they have", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Resources, that's a good point. He's got resources. All we've got is a , my friend, you find 'em. You find 'em and you end it now", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "The area's wired for surveillance, they'll be  for those moves", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "know what they're looking for and I'm telling you", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Who's calling", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "my friend's on vacation 'till Monday. I can give him the message when he gets back. That was my friend and the last nam", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "What about the tape", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "And if it wasn't", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Me neither, but the upshot is I've got color liv", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "I don't want any money. And believe me, I have no interest in ruining your life. I'm not interested in this tape", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Sir, we've just intercepted an that place communication", "docId": "Enemy-of-the-State.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "Well, sir, it seems there's a warrant out o", "qsentId": 92}]